easyclass.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy

**Personal Privacy**

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit www.easyclass.com website and/or register for membership. Please read the notification below carefully.

**Personal Information**

Within Easyclass.com website users are never asked for payment, donation, money or equivalents. Easyclass.com never requires and keeps record of any users’ ID number, credit card numbers, passwords and such relevant data.

In order to submit your user record to the System we need your name, surname and e-mail address. In order to provide you with services we may also request your name, geographical coordinates or telephone number. You are under no obligation to provide this information. Easyclass.com does not collect any other personal information that you do not expressly provide. Easyclass.com will never sell, rent, share, trade or barter your personal information, including your e-mail address, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission. Easyclass.com may share your personal information if required by law.

**Non-Personal Information**

Easyclass.com may also request non-personally identifiable information (such as annual income, buying preferences, or age), also known as demographic and profile data, though this information is optional. We may use this data to improve our site and/or tailor your experience at our site, showing you contents that we think you might be interested in, and displaying contents according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

**Usage Information**

In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, Easyclass.com may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers' use of Easyclass.com. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our service and website.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no future notices.

**Tracking**

Like most sites, www.easyclass.com makes use of browser "cookies." Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. Easyclass.com will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services.

**Links To Other Sites**

As part of the service, Easyclass.com may create links allowing you to access third party sites. Easyclass.com is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

**Modification To This Policy**

Easyclass.com may change this policy, but we will post any changes here.
